[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "What went through my mind when I fell down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer Lawrence"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "What was -- what was your most memorable moment of the whole day, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I think -- well, I think probably it's going to be the memory that everybody is going to remember, and that's Jennifer Lawrence, you know, tripping as she goes up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Why is she getting a bit of a kicking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, I think it's a little unfair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP$", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Why are we so bitchy about Anne Hathaway?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "You know, it's funny because we have this conversation at the show all the time because I'm always in defense of her because I have loved interviewing her and I think she's very sweet ad she --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anne Hathaway"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "And what were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "I was apparently trending worldwide on Twitter, I was told momentarily.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Are you -- are you leaping around the room, are you making acceptance speeches?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "No, not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "It was very unusual.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2005"], "PERSON": ["Seth"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "``", "NN", "NNP", "''", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Is there any truth to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "I did a cover story about Seth in 2005 for \"TV Guide\" and look, I've always, always found him to be a very interesting character.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Seth"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "I mean, Krista, are you a fan of Seth MacFarlane last night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Yes, I'm a big fan of Seth's.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Krista", "Seth MacFarlane"], "TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "How could you forget him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "I know, it's a lack of sleep.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "You like to see people uncomfortable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "That's how you have to react to these things, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Yes, it is kind of true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 343, "question": "What's your loser face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "(SMILING)", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Do you practice your loser face just in case the camera pans straight to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "No, that I haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Do you think it's bad luck?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "No, I just didn't think of it, but I'll start right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Have you got one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Just kind of a glazed smile, you know, yes, followed by some kind of protein bar.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Give me the face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Then I giggle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "Who was the Piers Morgan choice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "You know what, very interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers Morgan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Should she have been there at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "From my vantage point, absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Let me fill you in on what the first lady's strategy has been on this kind of thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Why are we getting so exercised about it, Donny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Obviously, she can, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "If she ever does that, I will come back on your show and I will physically eat my book one page at a time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNPS", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "If you were advising them, Washington Incorporated, about their brand, how do they get the message that America is sick and tired of this kind of behavior?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I actually don't think Americans are victims here.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Why does America need to have this astronomical ongoing defense budget when you have more pressing things at home to worry about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Sybrina, how are you planning to commemorate Trayvon's life and death tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "We're going to attend a candlelight ceremony here in New York.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "TO", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Where do you see it right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "From all the senseless gun violence that's been happening since our son's tragic loss, it's -- it's time for America to take a look at our gun laws, do something with the gun laws, take a look at the people that are purchasing guns, people that they are giving gun licenses to, because it's just too much senseless violence, just overwhelming the homes right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "How do you tackle that kind of mentality in light of this debate about Stand Your Ground?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Well, Piers, you try to be very open and honest about them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sybrina"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Because if he's not held accountable, what message does that send to the next child that's killed, unarmed, on the ground?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "A difficult question for you, Sybrina, but I want to put it to you anyway.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "In other words, if at the end of this trial George Zimmerman is exonerated of illegally killing your son, would you be prepared to publicly accept that verdict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Well, that's something that we have always asked for.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "What did you make of that, first of all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "I think it is interesting, Piers, that we heard the official statement that says the Holy Father is sick, that the Holy Father is frail.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "When you put it all together, where are we left here, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "Well, I take the Pope on his word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "Is celibacy really any longer a sensible thing for the Catholic church to enforce upon the priesthood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "I think it is for those who are called to be monks, to be religious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "I mean, is it time, in short, we had a more modern thinking Pope for the modern era?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "Well, let me respond to the statement about homosexuals in the clergy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNPS", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "If you were advising them, Washington Incorporated, about their brand, how do they get the message that America is sick and tired of this kind of behavior?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "I actually don't think Americans are victims here.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "Why does America need to have this astronomical ongoing defense budget when you have more pressing things at home to worry about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 793, "question": "Sybrina, how are you planning to commemorate Trayvon's life and death tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 794, "answer": "We're going to attend a candlelight ceremony here in New York.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "TO", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 802, "question": "Where do you see it right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 803, "answer": "From all the senseless gun violence that's been happening since our son's tragic loss, it's -- it's time for America to take a look at our gun laws, do something with the gun laws, take a look at the people that are purchasing guns, people that they are giving gun licenses to, because it's just too much senseless violence, just overwhelming the homes right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 814, "question": "How do you tackle that kind of mentality in light of this debate about Stand Your Ground?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 815, "answer": "Well, Piers, you try to be very open and honest about them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sybrina"]}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 825, "question": "Because if he's not held accountable, what message does that send to the next child that's killed, unarmed, on the ground?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 826, "answer": "A difficult question for you, Sybrina, but I want to put it to you anyway.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "In other words, if at the end of this trial George Zimmerman is exonerated of illegally killing your son, would you be prepared to publicly accept that verdict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "Well, that's something that we have always asked for.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 854, "question": "What did you make of that, first of all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 855, "answer": "I think it is interesting, Piers, that we heard the official statement that says the Holy Father is sick, that the Holy Father is frail.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 869, "question": "When you put it all together, where are we left here, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 870, "answer": "Well, I take the Pope on his word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 893, "question": "Is celibacy really any longer a sensible thing for the Catholic church to enforce upon the priesthood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 894, "answer": "I think it is for those who are called to be monks, to be religious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130225pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 906, "question": "I mean, is it time, in short, we had a more modern thinking Pope for the modern era?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 907, "answer": "EESE: Well, let me respond to the statement about homosexuals in the clergy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]